strategypage.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement for StrategyPage

**StrategyPage** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [StrategyPage](http://www.strategypage.com/)

Information Automatically Logged  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

Cookies  
Our Site uses cookies to keep track of where you have been on our site.

Advertisers  
We use third-party advertising companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Registration Forms  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), financial information (like their bank account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

Order Forms  
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the order forms is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

Surveys  
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. **StrategyPage** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Forums  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

Data Quality/Access  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  * You can send email to [support@strategyworld.com](mailto:support@strategyworld.com)

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
